Guide to the Stefan Brecht Papers MSS.355
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Performance Overview Subject Files A-Z
  - Leach, Wilford- ["Carmilla"] [annotated typescript] [3 of 4], 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Leach, Wilford- ["New Jerusalem"] [4 of 4], 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Lee, David- "Pyramid Theory", "Peebles Footnote to Song of Sweetback", circa 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Levine, Richard- "The Cancer of Ambition", 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Living Theatre, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Living Theatre- [1 of 3], circa 1992-2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Living Theatre- [2 of 3], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Living Theatre- "Third Rail 6" [3 of 3], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Living Theatre- Taylor Stoer, Paul Goodman [1 of 4], [undated] (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Living Theatre- Taylor Stoer, Paul Goodman [2 of 4], [undated] (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Living Theatre- Taylor Stoer, Paul Goodman [3 of 4], [undated] (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Living Theatre- Taylor Stoer, Paul Goodman [4 of 4], [undated] (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Living Theatre- [Body of God][1 of 16], circa 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Living Theatre-[Promotional Folder][2 of 16], 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Living Theatre- [3 of 16], 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Living Theatre- [A New Home for the Living Theatre] [4 of 16], March, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Living Theatre- [5 of 16], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Living Theatre- [6 of 16], [1985-1988] (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Living Theatre- "Songs of the Revolution" by Julian Beck [7 of 16], 1963, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Living Theatre- Julian Beck and Judith Malina "Only New York Performance" [8 of 16], June 26, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Living Theatre- [9 of 16], 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Living Theatre- [10 of 16], [1984-1986] (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Living Theatre- [11 of 16] "Masse Mensch", January, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Living Theatre- "The Yellow Methuselah" [12 of 16], January, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Living Theatre- "Archeology of Sleep" [13 of 16], Summer, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Living Theatre- [14 of 16], [undated] (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Living Theatre- Samuel Beckett's Theatre "1+2+ That Time" [15 of 16], March 28, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Living Theatre- [16 of 16] [The Living Theatre Abroad], [undated] (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Lutgenhorst, Manuel, [1981] (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Mead, Taylor, [circa 1976] (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Meat Productions, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Overlie, Mary, [1977-1978] (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Peppe, Michael, [1980-1983] (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Pietri, Pedro- "Appearing in Person Tonight, Your Mother" Clean Uncorrected Copy [1 of 5], [undated] (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Pietri, Pedro- "Jesus is Leaving" [2 of 5], [undated] (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Pietri, Pedro- "Telephone Booth Number" [3 of 5][original artwork], [undated] (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Pietri, Pedro- [4 of 5], [1986-1992] (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Pietri, Pedro- "Last Request" [typescript][5 of 5], [undated] (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Rainer, Yvonne- See also New American Theatre, [1972-1986] (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Rapapport, Mark, April 22-28, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Reich, Steve and Jon Gibson, [1975-1981] (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Ridiculous Theatrical Company- [1 of 2], [1984-1987] (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Ridiculous Theatrical Company- [2 of 2], [1982-1984] (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Rubenstein, Ken, [undated] (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sargent, Bob- ["Nothing to Lose"] [1 of 2], [1992-1993] (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Sargent, Bob- ["Phoetus", "Goddass"][2 of 2], [1989-1996] (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Serban, Andrei- [1 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Serban, Andrei- [2 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Mime Troupe, [1978] (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Shepard, Sam, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Skipitares, Theodora, [1983-1984] (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Harry, [1996] (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Jack- and E. Leffingwell, [1978, 1995, 1997] (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sprinkle, Annie- See also Performance Group, [1989] (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Squat [Theater], [circa 1980-1986] (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Structuralism- Kirby, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Talkin Band (Open Theatre), [circa 1979-1989] (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Templeton, Fiona, [1988, undated] (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Terayama, Shuji- and Tenjosa Jiki, [Circa 1980] (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Terayama, Shuji- "Theatre Journal: Theatre and Hegemony", December, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Texas Chainsaw Massacre- Tobe Hooper, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Theater For Your Mother- [1 of 2], [undated] (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Theater For Your Mother- "Ronald Reagan The Magazine of Poetry 2/6" [2 of 2], [undated] (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Theatre of Gibberish- J. Hobermann, B. Schneider, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Theissen, Bennett, [1987, undated] (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Tong, Winston, [1979] (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Van Itallie, Jean-Claude (Open Theatre), [Circa 1983] (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Weiss, Jeff- "Hot Keys", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Weiss, Jeff- "Dark Twist" and "Proximas Atracciones and Two Dykes with El Coyote", [undated] (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Weiss, Jeff- "And that's how the rent gets paid" and "Dr. Faustus lights the lights", [undated] (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Weiss, Jeff- ["Dark Twist" typescript Act 1] [1 of 2], [undated] (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Weiss, Jeff- ["Dark Twist" typescript Acts 2 and 3] [2 of 2], [undated] (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Wendko, Gina, [1982] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Whitman, Robert- [1 of 4], 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Whitman, Robert- [2 of 4], [1976-1984] (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Whitman, Robert- [Interview] [3 of 4], 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Whitman, Robert- [4 of 4], 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, Ann- "Electric Affinity" See also Jared Bark [1 of 3], [1976-1980] (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Wilson, Ann- "Electric Affinity" at The Kitchen, See also Jared Bark [2 of 3], [1975-1977] (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, Ann- "Electric Affinity" See also Jared Bark [3 of 3], [1975-1977] (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, Ann- "Butler's Lives of the Saints" [1 of 2], [undated] (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Wilson, Ann- "Butler's Lives of the Saints" [2 of 2], [undated] (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Zorn, John- [1 of 5], [undated] (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Zorn, John- "Trach and Field" [2 of 5], March, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Zorn, John- [3 of 5], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Zorn, John- [4 of 5], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Zorn, John- [Brecht's Notes: "Fidel", "Paradise Lost", "Antique Show", "School"] [5 of 5], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series II: Stuart Sherman
  This series comprises files that were compiled by Brecht while researching his book on artist Stuart Sherman. The files contain original artworks, including drawings and poetry pieces, which are often accompanied by correspondence. Correspondence includes both personal greetings and contributions towards Brecht's research. The series contains photographs documenting Sherman's "Spectacles," copies of Stuart Sherman's Quotidian Review, and newspaper clippings. There are two sets of interview transcripts, one conducted by Stefan Brecht and another by John Matturri. Included are Stefan Brecht's notes documenting Stuart Sherman events and personal interactions. Material ranges from the early 1970's to the late 1990's. Most material was produced in New York City, with a small amount from Stuart Sherman's time living in Germany. Interview transcripts can be found of correlating audio material.
  - Drawings of Stuart Sherman's Performance at MOMA Sculpture Garden by Alex Conway, August 4-5, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "One Acts and Two Trilogies" and "The Yellow Chair", [1987-1988] (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Stuart Sherman Spectacles" - by John Matturri, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - [Original Drawings by Stuart Sherman], [1970-1971] (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "A Strange Visit to M. De Charlus" by Marcel Proust and Stuart Sherman [typescript], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Charles Ludlam" by Stuart Sherman [typescript], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Man and Rose" by Stuart Sherman [Original work], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry A-Z WORD: 7 Sheets] [1 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry WORD: 23 Sheets] [2 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry A-Z: 28 Paginated Sheets][3 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry A-Z: 29-78 Paginated Sheets] [4 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry A-Z: 79-132 Paginated Sheets] [5 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry A-Z: 133-178 Paginated Sheets] [6 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry A-Z: 179-226 Paginated Sheets] [7 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry A-Z: 227-269 Paginated Sheets] [8 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - [Untitled Diagram Poetry A-Z: 270-307 Paginated Sheets] [9 of 9], [undated] (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, [Circa 1980-1989] (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Kolner Ensemble, [1989-1990] (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "Dead Still", December 7-17, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Stuart Sherman's Memorial, September, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "Statements on Sculpture" and "Invisible Theater", [1990, undated] (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Second Trilogy: Checkhov, Strindberg and Brecht", [1985-1986] (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - [Stuart Sherman in Berlin: "Berlin Walls" and Correspondence], [1986-1988] (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "An Evening of One-Act Plays", [1987] (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - [Invitations and Articles], [undated] (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - [Letter from Cindy Sherman], February 20, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Helene Winer developed by Cindy Sherman [1 of 3], [1979] (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Helene Winer developed by Cindy Sherman [2 of 3], [1979] (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Helene Winer developed by Cindy Sherman [3 of 3], [1979] (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Babette Mangolte [1 of 6], October 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Babette Mangolte [2 of 6], October 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Babette Mangolte [3 of 6], October 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Babette Mangolte [4 of 6], October 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Babette Mangolte [5 of 6], October 10, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) taken by Babette Mangolte [6 of 6], October 10, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman annotated, Circa December 1978-January 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Selections from Stuart Sherman's Eighth Spectacle (Portraits of People)", [undated] (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman on his 11th Spectacle, Second Tape of the Evening [Transcript], May 2, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman on his 11th Spectacle (The Erotic) Continues Last Interview: First Cassette of May 2nd [Transcript], May 2, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Interview- Third Session of Stuart Sherman's Explanation of his 11th Spectacle (The Erotic). Second Tape of the Evening [Transcript], March 6, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Interview- Third Session of Stuart Sherman's Explanation of his 11th Spectacle- Begins here [Transcript], March 6, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Interview- Second Session of Stuart Sherman's Explanation of his 11th Spectacle (The Erotic) [Transcript], February 22, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Interview- First Session of Stuart Sherman's Explanation of his 11th Spectacle [Transcript], February 22, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman on Four Movies of his [Transcript], October 19, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman Transcript [1 of 8], [September 25, 1978] (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman Transcript [2 of 8], [September 25, 1978] (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman Transcript [3 of 8], [September 25, 1978] (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman Transcript [4 of 8], [September 25, 1978] (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman Transcript [5 of 8], [September 25, 1978] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman Transcript [6 of 8], [September 25, 1978] (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman Transcript [7 of 8], [September 25, 1978] (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - John Matturri Interview with Stuart Sherman Transcript [8 of 8], [September 25, 1978] (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "Chekhov" [Trilogy], [1985] (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - "Imperfect Notes for a Perfect Manifesto and Oedipus" by Stuart Sherman [article from The Drama Review vol. 27, No.4], Winter, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Stuart Sherman's First Show [1 of 5], January 22, 1975; November 30, 1991; 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Stuart Sherman's First Show [2 of 5], [January 5, 1975] (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Stuart Sherman's First Show [3 of 5], [March 12, 1975] (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Stuart Sherman's First Show [4 of 5], [1975] (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Stuart Sherman's First Show [5 of 5], [undated] (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Letters: Preperation for Book on Stuart Sherman, [October, 1978-January 1979] (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman's First Show [Index to Transcript] [1 of 5], March 12, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman's First Show [Transcript] [2 of 5], March 12, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman's First Show [Transcript] [3 of 5], March 12, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman's First Show [Transcript][4 of 5], March 12, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman's First Show [Transcript] [5 of 5], March 12, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Interview- Stuart Sherman talks with Bob Schneider and Steve Anker, June 24, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - [Stuart Sherman's Sixth and Seventh Spectacles], [1975-1976] (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Stuart Sherman's Seventh Spectacle, May 21, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - SLIGHT: Eighth Spectacle at Open Space [Portraits of People], March, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Stuart Sherman's Tenth Spectacle [1 of 2], [October] 1977 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Stuart Sherman's Tenth Spectacle [2 of 2], [October] 1977 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Stuart Sherman's Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) [and 3=1 A Careful Misreading], 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - "Dinner with Stuart, Dec. 29, McBell's." [Brecht's Notes], December 30, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - [John Zorn and Stuart Sherman- Brecht's Notes], January 29, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - [Ken Kobland's "Near and Far"- Brecht's Notes], June 9, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - [Whitney Biennial "Glasses" and Films], [1979] (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - [Notes and Correspondence], [1979] (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - [Bernice Reynaude on Stuart Sherman], 1978 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Stefan Brecht on "Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)" and Stuart's early drawings for sets [1 of 3], [1985-1986, undated] (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Stefan Brecht on "Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)" and Stuart's early drawings for sets [2 of 3], [1982-1986, undated] (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Stefan Brecht on "Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)" and Stuart's early drawings for sets [3 of 3], [undated] (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "Thirteenth Spectacle (Time)", [undated] (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - [Invitations and Press Releases], [undated, 1994] (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ["Ninth Spectacle"], [undated] (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Stuart Sherman's "Hamlet (a portrait)" [with photographs], [1981-1982] (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Filmworks, [1980] (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - [Articles about Stuart Sherman], [1979-1982] (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - ["Faust" at Theater Am Turm], [1982] (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Stuart Sherman's "Tenth Spectacle", [undated] (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Stuart Sherman's Outline of Next Ten Movies, February 22, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - ["Carson McCullers" by Stuart Sherman in BOMB], Fall, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - [Fifteenth and Sixteenth Spectacles], [undated] (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - From Stuart Sherman to Stefan Brecht- [poetry] [1 of 2], April 21, 1992; March 12, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - From Stuart Sherman to Stefan Brecht- ["Away From Here, or, There"] [2 of 2], April 21, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - "SOLARIS"- [Book and typescript with cover letter from Stuart Sherman], May 12, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "Quotidian Review"- [First and Announcement], 1992 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - "Quotidian Review" Vol. 1 No. 2, October, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - "Quotidian Review" Vol. 1 No. 3, November, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - "Quotidian Review" Vol. 1 No. 4, December, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - "Quotidian Review" Vol. 1 No. 5, January-April, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - [Seventeenth Spectacle (Yes and Noh)], [undated] (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - "Christman is December" [with original work "Torso"], [1993-1995] (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - "The Book of Books" [with letter from Stuart Sherman], November 19, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - "American Fat"- [with correspondence], [1995-1996] (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - "The 1995 Eighth Annual Cleveland Performance Art Festival" (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Series III: Mabou Mines
  This series comprises files that were compiled by Brecht while working on his unfinished book on the avant-garde theater company Mabou Mines. Files consist of notes, newspaper clippings, original scripts, correspondence, and ephemera including posters, tickets, and invitations organized by specific production. Correspondence includes both personal greetings, solicitations for support, and contributions towards Brecht's research. The series starts with selections from the Performing Arts Services Files, each containing photographs with a one page description. Material ranges from early 1970s to early 2000s.
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Imagination Dead Imagine", 1984 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Pretty Boy", 1984 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Gospel at Colonus", 1983 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Hajj", 1982 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Cold Harbor", July, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Wrong Guys", May, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Prelude to Death in Venice", May, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Vanishing Pictures", February, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Dead End Kids", December, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Southern Exposure", February, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Shaggy Dog Animation", February, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Dressed Like an Egg", August, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Saint and The Football Player", February, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Cascando", November, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Beckett Plays", October, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "The Lost Ones", March, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Selections from Performing Art Services Files- "Red Horse Animation" and "B-Beaver", January 1974; December 1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation Part I and Part III" [Brecht's Notes][1 of 3], March, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation Part II" [Brecht's Notes][2 of 3], March, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation Part III" [Brecht's Notes][3 of 3], March, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes] [1 of 6], [March-February] 1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes] [2 of 6], [January 23] 1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" (Part I Section II) [Brecht's Notes] [3 of 6], [Janruary-March]1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" (Part II) [Brecht's Notes] [4 of 6], [January-March] 1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" (Part III) [Brecht's Notes] [5 of 6], [January-March] 1978 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes] [6 of 6], [January-March] 1978 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes annotated with Index] [1 of 8], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes annotated][2 of 8], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes annotated][3 of 8], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes annotated][4 of 8], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes annotated][5 of 8], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes annotated][6 of 8], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes annotated][7 of 8], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Brecht's Notes annotated][8 of 8], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation"- Interview with Lee Breuer [Transcript][1 of 2], May 23, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation"- Interview with Lee Breuer [Transcript][2 of 2], May 23, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [Handwritten Notes and Sketches] [1 of 4], 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [2 of 4], 1977-1878 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" Version A [Bound Typescript by Lee Breuer] [3 of 4], February 2, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - "Shaggy Dog Animation" [4 of 4], 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - "The Warrior Ant" and "Endgame", [May, 1985] (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Samuel Beckett- "Company" Frederick Neumann, November 20, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - "Artistic Statement and History of Mabou Mines", June, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Joanne Akalaitis- "Through the Leaves", [1984] (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - [Press Releases and Invitations], [undated] (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - "Theater" [Articles from Summer/Fall, 1982-1983] (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - [Samuel Beckett- "Endgame" articles about dispute], [undated] (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - [Mabou Mines Fifteenth Anniversary Benefit], [1985] (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bill Raymond- "Flow my tears, the policeman said", [June, 1985] (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - "Palermo and Jerusalem", [1984] (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - "Other Stages" Vol. 3 No. 9, January 15-28, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Lee Breuer- "Hajj", May 28, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - "Cold Harbor" [Bill Raymond and Dale Worsley], [1983] (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Re Cher Chez [Lee Breuer and Ruth Maleczech], [undated] (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "Red and Blue" [Joanne Akalaitis and Michael Herson], [1982] (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - [Mabou Mines Articles and Clippings], [1979-1982] (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Beverly Brown- "Vanishing Pictures" [Annotated draft], 1981 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Lee Breuer- "Lulu" [Articles by Shelley Berc], [1981, undated] (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "Southern Exposure", February 26, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "The B. Beaver Animation", [1990] (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Peter Tummons and Barbara Brecht-Shall [Methuen publication correspondence], November, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - "La Divina Caricatura"- by Lee Breuer [inscribed book], June, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)